Guide to the Treasurer, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Benefactors, 1700-1963; Series IV
  Subscriptions encompasses the records of many campaigns for financial support, both for general endowments and for special purposes, addressed to the multitude of Yale supporters. The records of any particular campaign usually include a list of subscribers with their pledges and may include the purposes and terms of donations, accounts of payments received and pledges unpaid, and notes by campaign agents on their travels and responses to their requests. (The accounting records of income and expenses of some campaigns are found in Series V, INVESTMENTS.)
  library. These records are arranged alphabetically by name of the project or fund.
  Special Gifts contains records of a few large or unusual gifts made by individuals during their lifetimes. The donations of Richard Salter and Timothy Dwight Porter came in the form of land and are particularly well documented. Salter proposed that the income derived from his gift of a farm in Windham, Connecticut, be used to promote the study of Hebrew and other oriental languages in Yale College. Porter'sgift put the use of a square block of Manhattan real estate under Yale's control. (In CORRESPONDENCE, 1841-1888: Select there are many letters from Thomas Thacher concerning this gift.) Sheldon Clark'sgifts in the form of assigned mortgages were the largest to that point in the college'shistory and created an endowed professorship and the first fellowships for non-professional postgraduate study. The histories of the DeForest, Hillhouse, and Leffingwell scholarship funds are also detailed in this sub-series. Papers respecting the John Trumbull and William Augustus Hillhouse annuities document how Yale came to own its fine collection of John Trumbull paintings and a large quantity of undeveloped real estate in New Haven. The records of the sub-series are arranged alphabetically by name of the donation or fund. (Correspondence concerning individual gifts will be found in CORRESPONDENCE, Filing Code: #239.)
  Estates Completed is by far the largest sub-series in this series. Most of the files date from the 1880s to 1950 with a few files earlier and later than these dates. The sub-series contains records of only those estates that had been settled at the time of the last transfer of records from the treasurer's office to Manuscripts and Archives. As of 1979 the sub-series Estates Completed was closed. Any completed estate papers that were retained by the office after this date, even those dating much earlier, will not be added to this sub-series. Instead they will be considered as part of the records of the Treasury Services (YRG5-E), the office where they are now filed.
  The files in this sub-series are arranged alphabetically by the name of the testator. Most files contain only a copy of the will or a note of what the treasurer reported to the corporation concerning the estate. In some instances there may be court proceedings and accounts compiled by the executors. In a few instances, usually where the treasurer or someone from the university acted as an executor, an estate'srecords may become voluminous. In such cases the files could contain personal papers, executor'scorrespondence, account books, and may other papers that an executor'smight have kept. Examples of such files include those for the estates of Edward Augustus Bowers, Sheldon Clark, Henry L. Ellsworth, William Lampson, Elias Loomis, Edla McPherson, O. C. Marsh, Mary Ann Goodman, and Augustus Russell Street. The files for the Edward S. Harkness estate are also very detailed.
  Though a few items of correspondence will be found in these files most correspondence concerning estates has been filed in the CORRESPONDENCE series. During the years ca. 1907 - 1937 the treasurer kept most correspondence on completed estates in subject files which are now Series III, Filing Code: #238. A few other estates" correspondence files were filed individually under the name of the estate in this code. The folder list which follows includes cross-references to the appropriate files in the CORRESPONDENCE series.
  - General Histories
    - Donations list and donations from the state of Connecticut, 1700- 1765 (Box 370, Folder 1)
    - Book kept by Ezra Stiles and others of early gifts to college, 1700-1804, with lists of library holdings and philosophical apparatus, forms for honorary degrees, diplomas, also copies of documents relating to the funds of 1792, Circa 1784-1804 (Box 370, Folder 2)
    - Documents respecting the funds of 1792, 1792-1796 (Box 370, Folder 3)
      See also: folio box 444a, folder 5
    - Notes, made by E. C. Herrick on the history of donations, Circa 1849-1858 (Box 370, Folder 4)
    - Rough sketch of register of donations,, prepared by E. C. Herrick, 1713-18511851 (Box 370, Folder 5)
    - Costs of buildings and donors of funds (also includes receipts from sales, gifts and payments of loans and loan purchases or other investments, 1868 Jan-1869 Apr; annual receipts and expenditures of various funds, ca. 1859-1884; rental of college rooms, 1877-1878), 1842-1905 (Box 371, Folder 6)
    - Histories and stipulations of donations and funds, ca. 1746-1908, Circa 1888-1908 (Box 371, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous notes concerning gifts, 1791-1887 (Box 371, Folder 8)
  - Subscriptions
    - General Endowments
      - Pleas, lists, receipts, 1818-1827 (Box 371, Folder 9)
      - Notes by Darius Mead, Lyman Warner and other agents on pledges received for various funds and on personal expenses and expenditures, 1831-1833 (Box 371, Folder 10)
      - Centum Millia Fund: agents notebooks of pledges, 1831-1833 (Box 371, Folder 11-13)
      - Centum Millia Fund: subscribers ledger, 1831-1832 (Box 371, Folder 14)
      - Centum Millia Fund: payments received, 1832-1833 (Box 372, Folder 15)
      - Centum Millia Fund: unpaid balances (also includes unpaid subscriptions to the Theological Building Fund), 1835-1838 (Box 372, Folder 16)
      - Centum Millia Fund: receipts (actual), 1832-1845 (Box 372, Folder 17)
      - Centum Millia Fund: memoranda, notes, Circa 1831-1836 (Box 372, Folder 18)
      - 1854 Fund: agents notebooks of pledges, Circa 1853-1854 (Box 372, Folder 19-20)
      - 1854 Fund: subscribers list and journal of payments, 1853-1860 (Box 372, Folder 21)
      - Woolsey Fund: correspondence, minutes of general committee meetings, printed circulars, subscription lists, Circa 1871-1878 (Box 372, Folder 22)
      - Bicentennial Fund: appeal, pledge lists, Circa 1899-1901 (Box 373, Folder 23)
      - Bicentennial Fund: subscription ledger, Circa 1899-1905 (Box 373, Folder 24)
      - Bicentennial Fund: record of payments received, Circa 1899-1904 (Box 373, Folder 25)
      - Yale Endowment and Extension Movement: pledge cards and stipulations concerning donations, 1905-1907 (Box 373, Folder 26)
      - Ledger of contributors to several funds including Law Library Endowment, Library Associates, Alumni Fund, Briton Hadden Memorial, Walter Camp Memorial, and the 1920 Fund, Circa 1924-1941 (Box 373, Folder 27)
    - Building Funds
      - House for Professor of Divinity: lists of subscribers, 1755-1756 (Box 374, Folder 28)
      - First Chapel: lists of subscribers, 1757-1765 (Box 374, Folder 29)
      - Dining Hall and Kitchen: list of subscribers, 1774 (Box 374, Folder 30)
      - Second Chapel: lists of subscribers (also includes list of subscribers for Gibbs" Cabinet), 1824-1825 (Box 374, Folder 31)
      - Second Chapel: letter of appointment, list of subscribers, and receipt for funds of agent Jacob Brace, Circa 1827-1828 (Box 374, Folder 32)
      - Theological Building (Divinity College): lists of subscribers, 1835-1836 (Box 374, Folder 33)
      - Theological Building (Divinity College): notes on unpaid subscriptions, 1835-1836 (Box 374, Folder 34)
        See also: box 372, folder 16
      - College Library (Dwight Hall): lists of subscribers, 1842-1843 (Box 374, Folder 35-36)
      - Battell Chapel: correspondence and pledge forms sent to agent Luther Manard Jones, 1867-1871 (Box 374, Folder 37)
      - Theological Building (West Divinity Hall): lists of subscribers, 1868, 1873 (Box 374, Folder 38)
    - Other Funds and Projects
      - Apparatus, philosophical: list of subscribers and payments record, 1786-1791 (Box 374, Folder 39)
      - Auger'sstatuary for Trumbull Gallery: conditions, lists of subscribers, 1837-1838 (Box 374, Folder 40)
      - Dwight (Jonathan B.) monument: list of subscribers, 1844 (Box 374, Folder 41)
      - Dwight Professorship of Didactic Theology: pledges, lists of subscribers, account of monies received (also includes a list of subscribers to Indigent, Pious Fund), 1822-1832 (Box 374, Folder 42)
      - Dwight Professorship of Didactic Theology: memorandum of an investigation of the account prepared by E. C. Herrick, 1852 (Box 374, Folder 43)
        See also: box 35, folder 59
      - Friends of Yale College: minutes of meetings (BRBL Transfer), 1817 (Box 374, Folder 43A)
      - Gibbs" Cabinet of Minerals: pledges, accounts of monies received, 1825-1831 (Box 374, Folder 44-45)
        See also: box 375, folder 50 box 375, folders 54-55 box 375, folder 59
      - Gibbs (Josiah Willard) portrait: lists of subscribers, 1855-1857 (Box 375, Folder 46)
      - Gratuity Fund (includes records of subscriptions to the Indigent, Pious Students Fund and Relief Fund): pledges, lists of subscribers, Circa 1830-1841 (Box 375, Folder 47-48)
        See also: box 375, folders 54-55 box 424, folders 6-7
      - Indigent, Pious Student Fund
        See: box 374, folders 42 box 375, folders 47-48 box 375, folders 54-55
      - Law library of Judge Hitchcock: letter to Joseph G. E. Larned and lists of subscribers, Circa 1845-1846 (Box 375, Folder 49)
      - Law Professorship: lists of subscribers (also includes list of subscribers for Gibbs Mineral Cabinet), Circa 1822-1826 (Box 375, Folder 50)
      - Lederer Mineral Cabinet: lists of subscribers, Circa 1843-1845 (Box 375, Folder 51)
      - Library enlargement: list of subscribers, 1822 (Box 375, Folder 52)
      - Organ for the Chapel: lists of subscribers, 1851-1854 (Box 375, Folder 53)
      - Relief Fund
        See: box 375, folders 47-48
      - Sacred Literature Professorship: lists and ledgers of subscribers (also includes lists of subscribers to Gibbs Mineral Cabinet and Indigent, Pious Student Fund), 1824-1834 (Box 375, Folder 54-55)
      - Sacred Literature Professorship: statements of accounts and receipts of agent Chauncey A. Goodrich, 1828-1831 (Box 375, Folder 56)
        See also: box 375, folder 59
      - School of applied science (Sheffield Scientific School): subscription book, 1856 (Box 375, Folder 57)
      - Taylor's[Nathaniel William?] bust: lists of subscribers, undated (Box 375, Folder 58)
      - Theological Department endowment: lists of subscribers (also includes list of subscribers to Dwight Professorship of Didactic Theology, Gibbs Mineral Cabinet, Sacred Literature Professorship), 1822-1834 (Box 375, Folder 59)
      - Theological Department endowment: lists of subscribers, 1858-1861 (Box 376, Folder 60)
      - Trumbull (John) bust by Hugh Peters: lists of subscribers, 1852 (Box 376, Folder 61)
      - Unidentified: notes on potential contributors and list of subscribers, Circa 1820-1891 (Box 376, Folder 62)
  - Special Gifts
    - Bergen (Francis) Memorial
      See: folio box 444a, folder 6a
    - Berkeley's(Bishop George) donation: notes, by E. C. Herrick, on history of the Berkeley Scholarship Fund: Henry White'sinterpretation of deed of gift, Circa 1852, 1871 (Box 376, Folder 62A)
      See also: box 426, folder 11
    - Clark's(Sheldon) donation: terms of the donation, lists of mortgages included, and accounts of the funds accrued, 1823-1829 (Box 376, Folder 63)
    - DeForest (David) Fund: terms of donation, history of fund, legal decisions, genealogy charts, Circa 1823-1907 (Box 376, Folder 64)
      See also: folio box 444a, folder 6
    - Hillhouse (Augustus Lucas) annuity: correspondence, agreements, memoranda and other papers concerning the transfer of unimproved real estate in New Haven to Yale College in return for a lifetime annuity, 1853-1860 (Box 376, Folder 65)
    - Hillhouse and Leffingwell Theological Scholarships: terms of donations by Mary L. Hillhouse of the James Hillhouse Scholarship and by Caroline M. Street of the William Leffingwell Scholarship, 1858 (Box 376, Folder 66)
    - Porter (T. D. and T. W.) Fund: record of property in New York City conveyed to H.C. Kingsley and by him held in trust for Yale College, with ledger of income and expense by piece of property, 1878-1879 (Box 376, Folder 67)
    - Salter (Richard) Fund: memorandum of the history, prepared by E. C. Herrick, with copies of the deed, lease, and receipts for rent of donated property in Windham, Connecticut, 1781-1792; 1851-1852 (Box 376, Folder 68)
    - Trumbull (John) annuity: agreements and deed of gift for paintings, 1831-1833, 1841 (Box 376, Folder 69)
      See also: folio box 444a, folder 7
    - Webster (Noah) donation
      See: box 106, folder 195a
  - Estates Completed
    - Abbey, Mary Gertrude, 1939 (Box 377, Folder 70)
    - Abbott, Paul W., 1922 (Box 377, Folder 71)
    - Abernethy, John J., [1907?] (Box 377, Folder 72)
    - Achelis, John, 1933 (Box 377, Folder 73)
    - Adams, Lyell, [1892] (Box 377, Folder 74)
    - Allen, Frank D., 1910-1911 (Box 377, Folder 75)
      See also: box 314, folders 2018-2022 box 340, folder 2264
    - Alling, Elsie M., 1954, 1956 (Box 377, Folder 76)
    - Allison, John M.S., 1944-1945 (Box 377, Folder 77)
    - Allison, William B., 1934, 1938-1944 (Box 377, Folder 78)
    - Alvord, John F., 1955 (Box 377, Folder 79)
    - Ames, Edward, 1940 (Box 377, Folder 80)
    - Anderson, Eunice M., 1918 (Box 377, Folder 81)
      See also: box 314, folder 2018-2022
    - Andrews, Eleanor, 1918, 1924 (Box 377, Folder 82)
    - Andrews, Jane E., 1930-1931 (Box 377, Folder 83)
    - Andrews, Lancelot, 1920 (Box 377, Folder 84)
    - Andrews, William Loring, 1920 (Box 377, Folder 85)
      See also: box 314, folders 2018-2022
    - Angell, Joel H, 1884, 1909 (Box 377, Folder 86)
    - Anthony, Andrew W., 1932 (Box 377, Folder 87)
    - Archibald, Julia A., 1920-1921 (Box 377, Folder 88)
    - Armour, Allison V., 1941 (Box 377, Folder 89)
    - Arnold, Harriette M., 1942-1946 (Box 378, Folder 90)
    - Arnot, Matthias H., 1900, 1910-1911 (Box 378, Folder 91)
    - Arvidson, Robert T., 1953 (Box 378, Folder 92)
    - Atterbury, Albert H., 1952, 1954 (Box 378, Folder 93)
    - Atwater, Jason, 1861 (Box 378, Folder 94)
    - Atwater, John P., 1897 (Box 378, Folder 95)
    - Avery, Harry E., 1933, 1935 (Box 378, Folder 96)
    - Avery, Myra H., 1933-1936 (Box 378, Folder 97)
    - Ayres, Harriet L., 1927-1928 (Box 378, Folder 98)
    - Bacon, Asa, 1857-1858 (Box 378, Folder 99)
    - Bacon, Francis, 1911, 1913-1914 (Box 378, Folder 100)
    - Bacon, Theodore D., 1930 (Box 378, Folder 101)
    - Bacon, William T., 1911-1925 (Box 378, Folder 102)
      See also: box 308, folder 1935
    - Bahn, Laura S., 1952-1954 (Box 378, Folder 103)
    - Bailey, Mary E., 1933 (Box 378, Folder 104)
    - Baldwin, Annie L., 1956-1957 (Box 378, Folder 105)
    - Baldwin, Annie S., 1922, 1930 (Box 378, Folder 106)
    - Baldwin, George W., 1930 (Box 378, Folder 107)
    - Baldwin, Lulu K., 1944, 1950 (Box 378, Folder 108)
    - Baldwin, Simeon E., 1896, 1902, 1916 (Box 378, Folder 109)
    - Bangs, John Kendrick, Jr., 1942 (Box 378, Folder 110)
    - Bannard, Otto T., 1926, 1929-1930, 1961, 1963 (Box 379, Folder 111)
    - Barclay, Albert H., 1948, 1951 (Box 379, Folder 112)
    - Barclay, Blanche, 1945 (Box 379, Folder 113)
    - Bardwell, Harry J., 1930 (Box 379, Folder 114)
    - Barge, Benjamin F., 1902, 1907 (Box 379, Folder 115)
    - Barnes, Courtlandt D., 1946, 1952 (Box 379, Folder 116)
    - Barnes, John Sanford, 1943 (Box 379, Folder 117)
    - Barnes, Jonathan, 1914 (Box 379, Folder 118)
    - Barnum, William M., 1925, 1926 (Box 379, Folder 119)
    - Barr, Charles J., 1925 (Box 379, Folder 120)
    - Barrell, Finley, 1924, 1942 (Box 379, Folder 121)
    - Barrell, Grace W., 1930, 1936 (Box 379, Folder 122)
    - Bartlett, Clara C., 1934 (Box 379, Folder 123)
    - Battell, Joseph, 1854, 1875, 1890 (Box 379, Folder 124)
    - Bayley, Norman B., 1909, 1916 (Box 379, Folder 125)
    - Bayne, Hugh, 1953, 1956-1957 (Box 379, Folder 126)
    - Beam, Willoughby, 1925 (Box 379, Folder 127)
    - Beardsley, Clifford R., 1950 (Box 379, Folder 128)
    - Beckwith-Ewell, Glover C., 1924 (Box 379, Folder 129)
    - Bedell, Emmeline Reed, 1920-1921 (Box 379, Folder 130)
    - Bedell, Margaret S., 1932-1933, 1938 (Box 379, Folder 131)
    - Beebe, Maria Louise, 1917 (Box 379, Folder 132)
    - Beebe, William, 1912, 1917 (Box 379, Folder 133)
    - Belden, Ebenezer B., 1888-1893, 1907-1908 (Box 379, Folder 134)
      See also: box 289, folder 1753 box 314, folders 2018-2022
    - Belding, Edward L., 1923-1924 (Box 379, Folder 135)
    - Bell, Nelson W., 1924 (Box 380, Folder 136)
    - Bellis, Horace D., 1949 (Box 380, Folder 137)
    - Beman, A. F., 1874 (Box 380, Folder 138)
    - Benet, William Rose, 1950 (Box 380, Folder 139)
    - Bentley, Edward S., Jr., 1943-1944 (Box 380, Folder 140)
    - Bergen, Frank, 1934 (Box 380, Folder 141)
    - Berkman, Joseph, 1951, 1955 (Box 380, Folder 142)
    - Bernstein, Albion O., 1940, 1941 (Box 380, Folder 143)
    - Betts, Samuel Rossitter, 1930-1931 (Box 380, Folder 144)
    - Bibbins, William B., 1858, 1871 (Box 380, Folder 145)
    - Bigelow, Emma F. G., 1938 (Box 380, Folder 146)
    - Bigelow, Lucius H. Sr., 1956 (Box 380, Folder 147)
    - Bigelow, Russell A., 1891 (Box 380, Folder 148)
    - Billings, E. C., 1899, 1916 (Box 380, Folder 149)
    - Bishop, William H., 1913, 1917, 1923, 1928-1929 (Box 380, Folder 150)
    - Bissell, Josiah H., 1907 (Box 380, Folder 151)
    - Black, Helen N., 1952 (Box 380, Folder 152)
    - Black, Schuyler L., 1946 (Box 380, Folder 153)
    - Bliss, Charles M., 1890, 1907 (Box 380, Folder 154)
      See also: box 261, folder 1518
    - Bliss, George T., 1896-1897, 1899, 1901 (Box 380, Folder 155)
    - Bloch, Solomon M., 1938, 1939, 1941 (Box 380, Folder 156)
    - Blount, Archibald H., 1897-1899, 1907 (Box 380, Folder 157)
    - Boardman, Lucy H., 1907, 1909 (Box 380, Folder 158)
      See also: box 313, folder 2012
    - Booth, Minot, undated (Box 380, Folder 159)
    - Borden, Matthew C. D., 1894, 1896, 1912 (Box 380, Folder 160)
    - Borup, Henry D., 1916, 1924, 1933 (Box 380, Folder 161)
    - Bourne, Emily Howland, 1920-1922 (Box 380, Folder 162)
    - Bournique, Stella C., 1958 (Box 380, Folder 163)
    - Bowers, Edward A., 1907, 1922-1927 (Box 381, Folder 164)
    - Bowers, Edward A.: correspondence, 1924 August-December (Box 381, Folder 165)
    - Bowers, Edward A.: counterfoils and bankbooks, 1922-1924 (Box 381, Folder 166)
    - Bowers, Edward A.: bankstatements, 1922-1924 (Box 381, Folder 167)
    - Bradford, Edward A., 1927-1928 (Box 381, Folder 168-169)
    - Bradford, Edward A., 1929-1939, 1943-1950 (Box 382, Folder 170-174)
    - Bradley, Elizabeth C., 1911 (Box 383, Folder 175)
    - Bradley, Susan L., 1915 (Box 383, Folder 176)
      See also: box 315, folder 2023-2029
    - Brewer, Maud Dorman, 1947 (Box 383, Folder 177)
    - Brewster, James H., 1958 (Box 383, Folder 178)
    - Brewster, Kate L., 1947 (Box 383, Folder 179)
    - Brinton, Gertrude W., 1942 (Box 383, Folder 180)
    - Brinton, Howard F., 1923, 1942, 1954-1955 (Box 383, Folder 181)
    - Bronson, Edward B., 1925 (Box 383, Folder 182)
    - Brooker, Charles F., 1926 (Box 383, Folder 183)
    - Brooks, Charles W., 1949 (Box 383, Folder 184)
    - Brooks, Henry S., 1938 (Box 383, Folder 185)
    - Brott, George O., 1915, 1919, 1941, 1947 (Box 383, Folder 186)
    - Brown, Anna W., 1940-1944 (Box 383, Folder 187)
    - Brown, Benjamin W. B., 1937 (Box 383, Folder 188)
    - Brown, Charles R., 1948 (Box 383, Folder 189)
    - Brown, Edwin H., 1939 (Box 383, Folder 190)
    - Brown, Henry Billings, 1910-1914 (Box 383, Folder 191)
      See also: box 315, folders 2023-2029
    - Brown, Herman J., 1960 (Box 383, Folder 192)
    - Brown, Marie C., 1939, 1943-1947 (Box 383, Folder 193)
    - Brown, Robert, Jr., 1876, 1880, 1886, 1911 (Box 383, Folder 194)
    - Brown, Thatcher Magoun, 1953 (Box 383, Folder 195)
    - Brownfield, Robert L., 1946, 1961 (Box 383, Folder 196)
    - Brubacher, Abram R., 1939 (Box 383, Folder 197)
    - Brush, Graham, 1954 (Box 383, Folder 198)
    - Bryant, Annie B. M., 1932-1934 (Box 383, Folder 199)
    - Buckham, Robert B., 1940 (Box 383, Folder 200)
    - Bunker, Kate McElroy, 1954 (Box 383, Folder 201)
    - Burgess, Carrie T., 1945 (Box 383, Folder 202)
    - Burns, S. Fanny, 1932 (Box 383, Folder 203)
    - Burroughs, William, 1959, 1961 (Box 383, Folder 204)
    - Burrowes, H. S., 1951 (Box 383, Folder 205)
    - Bushrell, Samuel K., 1942, 1957 (Box 383, Folder 206)
    - Butler, Henry H., 1914-1916 (Box 383, Folder 207)
    - Byers, Martha F., 1911-1912 (Box 383, Folder 208)
    - Calkins, Charlotte W., 1937 (Box 384, Folder 209)
    - Callender, John A., 1955-1958 (Box 384, Folder 210)
    - Camp, Samuel C., 1756, 1823, 1841-1842 (Box 384, Folder 211)
    - Campbell, Eugenia W., 1935 (Box 384, Folder 212)
    - Campbell, Hugh, 1931-1945 (Box 384, Folder 213)
    - Campbell, James, 1899, 1916 (Box 384, Folder 214)
    - Campbell, James E., 1914, 1934 (Box 384, Folder 215)
    - Carmalt, William H., 1929 (Box 384, Folder 216)
    - Carpenter, Mary W., 1931, 1935 (Box 384, Folder 217)
    - Carpenter, Zachary T., 1890, 1891 (Box 384, Folder 218)
    - Case, Charles B., 1931 (Box 384, Folder 219)
    - Castle, Frank E., 1923 (Box 384, Folder 220)
    - Catlin, George L., 1896 (Box 384, Folder 221)
    - Chambers, Robert A., 1951 (Box 384, Folder 222)
    - Chandlers, Woods, 1928, 1932 (Box 384, Folder 223)
    - Chapin, Charles H. B., 1943-1945 (Box 384, Folder 224)
    - Chapman, Daisy Rogers, 1933, 1944, 1949 (Box 384, Folder 225)
    - Chase, Frederick L., 1928, 1934 (Box 384, Folder 226)
    - Chase, Irving Hall, 1948 (Box 384, Folder 227)
    - Cherry, Alfred F., 1945, 1947 (Box 384, Folder 228)
    - Chester, Manley E., 1938 (Box 384, Folder 229)
    - Chittenden, Anna H., 1897 (Box 384, Folder 230)
    - Chittenden, Russell H., 1938, 1944 (Box 384, Folder 231)
    - Christman, Joseph A., 1855, 1889-1891 (Box 384, Folder 232)
    - Churchill, Lawrence W., 1936 (Box 384, Folder 233)
    - Clark, Alfred T., 1954 (Box 384, Folder 234)
    - Clark, Charles W., 1906 (Box 384, Folder 235)
    - Clark, Frank E., 1926, 1935 (Box 384, Folder 236)
    - Clark, George C., 1944 (Box 384, Folder 237)
    - Clark, John P., 1931-1932 (Box 384, Folder 238)
    - Clark, Noyes D., 1937-1938 (Box 384, Folder 239)
    - Clark, Sheldon, 1840-1841 (Box 385, Folder 240)
    - Clark, Sheldon: executor'saccounts, 1840-1841 (Box 385, Folder 241)
    - Clark, Sheldon: records of land holdings, mortgages, rent, and interest income, Circa 1806-1838 (Box 385, Folder 242)
    - Clark, Sheldon: records of Thomas Clark's estate; records of Sherman Clark's estate, 1767, 1806-1813, 1822 (Box 385, Folder 243)
    - Clark, Sheldon: records of Thomas Clark's land holdings, 1760-1811 (Box 385, Folder 244)
    - Clark, Sheldon: correspondence, 1808-1837 (Box 385, Folder 245)
    - Clark, Sheldon: other personal papers, 1810-1840 (Box 385, Folder 246)
    - Clark, Stephen C., 1960 (Box 385, Folder 247)
    - Clark, Susan C., 1895 (Box 385, Folder 248)
    - Clark, Thomas Benedict, 1931 (Box 385, Folder 249)
    - Clay, Elizabeth M., 1936 (Box 385, Folder 250)
    - Clement, Norman P., 1949, 1951 (Box 385, Folder 251)